{
    "subject": "resource/Tom_Jones_(singer)",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/linguistics/gold/hypernym",
    "object": "resource/Singer",
    "human_readable": "Tom Jones is a Singer.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9213700294494629,
            "question": "Is Tom Jones known for singing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9182769656181335,
            "question": "Is Tom Jones a musician?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8119778633117676,
            "question": "When did Tom Jones start his career as a singer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6036245822906494,
            "question": "Has Tom Jones won any awards for his singing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5577099323272705,
            "question": "What type of music does Tom Jones perform?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5154939889907837,
            "question": "Where is Tom Jones from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4499576985836029,
            "question": "What is Tom Jones famous for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.37998196482658386,
            "question": "What are some of Tom Jones' most popular songs?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.37713441252708435,
            "question": "What is Tom Jones' profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.19146795570850372,
            "question": "Has Tom Jones acted in any movies or television shows?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Tom Jones is a Singer.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4537_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Tom Jones' profession?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4537_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some of Tom Jones' most popular songs?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4537_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Tom Jones famous for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4537_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4537_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4537_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4537_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4537_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4537_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4537_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4537_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4537_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4537_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4537_99.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents provide multiple references to Tom Jones being a Welsh singer who has had a long and successful career across various genres of music. This supports the statement that \"Tom Jones is a Singer.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}